Kaloyan Penev

Software Engineer



ABOUT ME

Problem-solver with an interest for machine learning and computer graphics. Professional experience using Unity for Bournemouth University on the VISTA AR project. Familiar with both Object Oriented and Entity-Component-System programming paradigms. Most recently finished development of my dissertation research project – Hand Posture Recognition in Real Time from RGB images using YOLOv4.

EXPERTISE

- Convolutional Neural Networks
- Game Engine programming
- Unity
- Metaheuristics
- Graphics programming
- Pathfinding

- **+**44 7500 652536
- @ kdpenev@gmail.com
- https://penev.me

EXPERIENCE

JUNIOR UNITY DEVELOPER

Bournemouth University • Feb 2020 - Jul 2020

- Development and profiling of AR apps
- Performance optimization for mobile devices
- Shader programming with HLSL and Shader Graph

STUDENT AMBASSADOR

Bournemouth University • Sep 2018 - Present

- Active engagement in the Admissions division
- Garnered rich communication experience
- Improved presenting and public speaking skills

EDUCATION

BSc GAMES SOFTWARE ENGINEERING

Bournemouth University • Sept 2018 – Jun 2021 Predicted First class Honours

- Graphics and Computational Programming 83.03%
- Game Engine Programming 79.00%
- Al Game Programming 75.50%

LANGUAGES







